It was half past one.
Give time still manager here,
please,
about what about maintenance maintenance is
I was supposed to be here half past one.
Isn't that what they passed me?
They didn't say it was to do the repair,
but what did I come here to fix your day for?
I'm Caio from the Brigadier's workshop.
This little chocolate ball here contains twenty grams of happiness.
How much happiness do you need on your day today
losing the three reals.
Fresh,
smell it?
Dude,
take it to the team,
it already gives motivation,
right? Face?
That's ten pears there.
No, no,
not what you said I'll want ten,
I'll want ten.
Guys,
I'm here inside the Nike store,
brother with Felipe I came to do some maintenance and
he just said he's ten fucking brother.
Thanks.
Véi valeu saved my quota today and you can leave it right here.
I'm with my brother,
I'm with you,
oh if you want to follow Instagram it's Caio in the world.
Yes,
you're going there
Valeu mano.
Thanks old.